<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bones Fundamentals on 節奏骨小記</title><link>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/</link><description>Recent content in Bones Fundamentals on 節奏骨小記</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-Hant</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 &lt;a href="https://github.com/heyitsjoshchuang">Josh Chuang&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 19:00:19 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grip</title><link>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/grip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:53:40 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/grip/</guid><description>The bones can be held in the hand in various ways. For the purpose of this wiki, only one is covered.
Description Slot one bone between the base section (proximal phalanx) of the index and middle fingers, and the other between the middle and ring fingers. The two bones should curve away from each other. Curve the fingers at the base and middle joint as if you are making a fist, and the middle and ring fingers lay on the side of the bones.</description></item><item><title>Tap</title><link>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/tap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 19:23:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/tap/</guid><description>The tap is a move that makes a single click. It is part of the triplet, the forward duplet, the upside-down duplet, and the quadruplet.
M:4/4
L:1/4
Q:1/4=120
K:perc stafflines=1
B z B z|B B B z|]
w: t t|t t t
An example tune, demonstrating how taps may be notated.
Movement The tap can be initiated from a wide range of hand angles, from upright to rotated nearly 180 degrees forward. A sharp snapping foward rotation is applied, causing the free bone to flicked towards the fixed bone, making a single click.</description></item><item><title>Backward Duplet</title><link>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/backward-duplet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 06:20:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/backward-duplet/</guid><description>The backward duplet is a move that makes two clicks with a single backward rotation. It is part of the triplet and the quadruplet.
M:4/4
L:1/8
Q:1/4=120
K:perc stafflines=1
(3BBz z2 (3BBz z2|]
w: k r k r
An example tune, demonstrating how backward duplets may be notated.
Movement The backward duplet is initiated with the hand upright or rotated slightly backwards. A sharp snapping backward rotation is applied, causing the fixed bone to strike free bone directly, making the first click.</description></item><item><title>Triplet</title><link>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/triplet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 07:39:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://heyitsjoshchuang.github.io/notes-on-bones/zh-hant/wiki/bones-fundamentals/triplet/</guid><description>The triplet is a move that makes clicks in groups of three. Consecutive triplets are also called the roll.
M:4/4
L:1/8
Q:1/4=120
K:perc stafflines=1
(3BBB B2 (3BBB B2|(3BBB (3BBB (3BBB B2|]
w: t k r t t k r t | t k r t k r t k r t
An example tune, demonstrating how triplets may be notated.
Movement At slower tempos, the triplet resembles a tap and a backward duplet played back to back, with the second click happening when the hand is angled backwards from upright.</description></item></channel></rss>